Guide to the Mary McCarthy Papers, circa 1915-2013 (bulk 1960-1989)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES IV: SUBJECT FILES AND RESEARCH MATERIAL
  - Subject Files
    - Vietnam: Medical Aid, 1967-1970 (Folder 179.5)
    - Vietnam: Medical Aid, 1971-1975 (Folder 179.6)
    - Vietnam: Ho Chi Minh, "Man of the Decade", 1969 (Folder 179.7)
    - Vietnam: Miscellaneous clippings, 1964-1977; (6 folders ) (Folders 179.8 - 179.13)
    - Vietnam: Miscellaneous clippings, undated (Folder 179.14)
    - Watergate — scrapbooks, (6 volumes and multiple unbound packages) (Boxes 313-314)
  - Clippings
    - Clippings, etc.: Literature, culture and society (Folder 179.15)
    - Clippings, etc.: Alternative press (including "the s.c.u.m. manifesto" by Valerie Saldano (Folder 179.16)
    - Clippings, etc.: Unites States politics (Folder 179.17)
    - Clippings, etc.: United States - civil rights and Black power (Folder 179.18)
    - Clippings, etc.: Latin America (Folder 179.19)
    - Clippings, etc.: South Africa (Folder 179.20)
    - Clippings, etc.: Western Europe (Folder 179.21)
    - Clippings, etc.: Spain and Portugal (Folder 179.22)
    - Clippings, etc. — miscellaneous (Folder 179.23)
    - Clippings — 1968 (Box 311)
    - Clippings — Art and artists (Box 315)
    - Clippings — The Hague (Box 312)
    - Clippings — Italy floods, 1985 (Box 312)
    - Clippings — Magazines (Box 312)
    - Clippings — Maine (Box 312)
    - Clippings — Middle East and China (Box 312)
    - Clippings — Paris bombing, 1986 (Box 312)
    - Clippings — Partisan Review (Box 312)
    - Clippings — Poland (Box 312)
    - Clippings — Social comment, (includes correspondence) (Box 312)
    - Clippings — Vassar College (Box 312)
    - Clippings — Vietnam, (4 folders) (Box 312)
    - Clippings — Watergate (Box 312)
    - Clippings — writers — articles and reviews, 1961-1988, undated; (3 folders) (Box 315)
    - Clippings — writers, family and friends (Box 315)
    - Clippings — writers, family and friends — individual files, (42 folders) (Box 315)
    - Clippings — obituaries, (4 folders) (Box 315)
    - Clippings — miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 315)
  - Works by and about Others
    - Arendt, Hannah, "La Vie de l’Esprit" (Folder 331.1)
    - Berenson, Bernard. "On the Future of I Tatti" w/brochure (Folder 97.1)
    - Dabney, Lewis. The Portable Wilson, chapter 1: typescript draft with letter (6/5/80) (Folder 97.2)
    - Didion, Joan. Democracy: A Novel (1984) [used by McCarthy for her review of this work]: Advance uncorrected proofs: (Folder 97.3)
    - Farrell, James. "Scene at the Coupole": signed photocopy (Folder 97.4)
    - Frank, Joseph. "Dostoevsky's Realism": inscribed and signed (Folder 97.5)
    - Frank, Joseph. "The Novel in Wonderland": inscribed and signed (Folder 97.6)
    - Frank, Joseph. "Nicola Chiaromonte: The Paradox of History": typescript photocopy (Folder 97.7)
    - Kalsone, David. "Trial Balances: Elizabeth Bishop and Marianne Moore," Grand Street, undated (Folder 97.8)
    - Kimber, Rita and Robert, trans. Arendt/Jaspers Letters - forward (Folder 329.5)
    - Kimber, Rita and Robert, trans. Arendt/Jaspers Letters - footnotes, p. 1-226 (Folders 329.6 - 329.10)
    - Kimber, Rita and Robert, trans. Arendt/Jaspers Letters, p. 531-600 (Folders 329.11 - 329.12)
    - Kimber, Rita and Robert, trans. Arendt/Jaspers Letters, p. 601-1127 (Folders 330.1 - 330.11)
    - Mallon, Thomas. [article]: "A Boy of No Importance,", (photocopy) (Folder 97.9)
    - Mallon, Thomas. [article]: "The Limits of History in the Novels of Joan Didion": inscribed and signed (Folder 97.10)
    - Mallon, Thomas. "The Novel on Elba": typescript photocopy (Folder 97.11)
    - McCarthy, James Kevin. "The Joy of the Ride: The Beginning": typescript photocopy (Folder 97.12)
    - [McCarthy, Mary, "Constantin Jelenski, l'ami Kot" Liberation ] KOT, 1987 (Folder 329.4)
    - McCarthy, Mary, K.A. Jelenski in loving memory (Folder 329.3)
    - McClosky, Michael. "Destiny or Death": Pamphlet inscribed to McCarthy by the author (Folder 97.23)
    - Meacham, Stewart. "Peace with Honor in Vietnam": mimeographed typescript (Folder 97.13)
    - Merrill, James. "To My Greek" draft, (typescript) (Folder 302.1)
    - Nooteboom, Cees. "The Knight Has Died" [extract]: typescript copy (Folder 97.14)
    - Nooteboom, Cees. "Rituelen" and "A Prisoner in Love": typescript photocopies (Folder 97.15)
    - Nooteboom, Cees. Correspondence and material relating to Nooteboom's Pegasus Prize for Literature, 1982 (Folders 97.16 - 97.17)
    - Novak, Michael Paul. "Love and Influence: Louise Bogan, Rolfe Humphries, and Theodore Roethke": Photocopy (Folder 97.21)
    - Phillips, William. [Essay on Saul Bellow]: typescript photocopy (Folder 97.18)
    - Rado, Sandor. Schizotypal Organization (Folder 331.2)
    - Rousuck, E.J. Eulogy by Brendan Gill: pamphlet (Folder 97.22)
    - Santini, Lee R. "La Passione di Capire": Inscribed and signed typescript photocopy (Folder 97.19)
    - Strauss, Karen. "The Evolution of Love" [and other photocopied typescript drafts of poetry] (Folder 97.20)
    - s.n. Jane Austen and the Anti-Hero Tradition (Folder 329.2)
    - Biographies of Various Authors (Folder 329.1)
- SERIES V: PERSONAL CORRESPONDENCE
  - Personal correspondence to and from Mary McCarthy
    - Able, Lionel, 1948 Dec 3 (Folder 342.1)
    - Adler, Renata, 1979 (Folder 180.1)
    - Adler, Renata: See also correspondence between McCarthy and Reuel Wilson
    - Allen Robert L., 1974-1979 (Folder 180.2)
    - Alsop, Joseph, 1953, undated (Folder 342.2)
    - Anderson, Susan J., 1985-1988 (Folder 180.3)
    - Anderson, Susan J., 1989 (Folder 342.3)
    - Anderson, Susan J., 1989 (Folder 365.1)
    - Andrews, Wayne, 28 November 1949 (Folder 352.12)
    - Angleton, Carmen - incoming, 1957-1988, undated (Folders 180.6 - 180.12)
    - Angleton, Carmen - outgoing, 1955-1987; (photocopies) (Folders 180.13 - 180.15)
    - Angleton, Carmen, 1988-1989, undated (Folder 342.4)
    - Antman, David, 1954 March 25 (Folder 342.5)
    - Aranguren, José Luis L., 1964-1967 (Folder 180.4)
    - Arbasino, Alberto, 1959-1987 (Folder 180.5)
    - Arbasino, Alberto, 1989 April 28 (Folder 342.6)
    - Arendt, Hannah, 1948-1958, undated (Folder 342.7)
    - Arendt, Hannah, 1949-1975, undated (Folders 181.1 - 181.18)
    - Ascoli, Max, 1952-1953 (Folder 342.8)
    - Ashbery, John, undated (Folder 182.1)
    - Aswell, Mary Louise (Harpers Bazaar), 1943, 1948 (Folder 342.9)
    - Athanassopoulos, Dimitri, 1980 (Folder 182.2)
    - Atlas, James, 1974-1979 (Folder 182.3)
    - Auchincloss, Eve, no year 5 October (Folder 182.4)
    - Auchincloss, Louis S., 1965-1984 (Folder 182.5)
    - Augstein, Katharina, 1971-1984, undated (Folder 182.6)
    - Austin, Helen and Mollie, 1974-1978, undated (Folder 182.7)
    - Austin, Sally, 1970-1985, undated (Folder 182.8)
    - Ayer, Sir Alfred ("Freddie"), 1986 (Folder 182.9)
    - Ayer, Nick, 1989 July 10 (Folder 342.10)
    - Baggs, Joan (Mrs. William), 1969 (Folder 182.10)
    - Baldwin, James, 1976 (Folder 182.11)
    - Ballinger, Francis Street, undated (Folder 342.11)
    - Ballon, Hillary, 1989 (Folder 342.12)
    - Barolini, Antonio, 1958 Nov 10 (Folder 342.13)
    - Barnett, Jim (Connecticut State College), 1938 March 13 (Folder 342.14)
    - Barth, Adrienne and Alan, 1973-1979, undated (Folder 182.12)
    - Bartlett, Grace, 1949 June 20 (Folder 342.15)
    - Barnes, Patricia, undated (Folder 342.16)
    - Baumgarter, Bernice "Bebe" (Brandt and Brandt), 1954, 1956 (Folder 342.17)
    - Beaumel, Beatrice, no year May 26 (Folder 182.13)
    - Belanger, Cecelia, 1968 (Folder 182.14)
    - Bell, Charles H., 1954 Feb 13 (Folder 342.18)
    - Bellow, Saul, undated (Folder 342.19)
    - Bellow, Saul: See also Folder 378.2 for a draft letter from McCarthy to Bellow regarding Hannah Arendt
    - Beloff, Max, 1963-1964 (Folder 182.15)
    - Bently, Eric (Columbia University), 1956 May 20 (Folder 342.20)
    - Berenson, Bernard, 1955-1958 (Folder 342.25)
    - Berenson, Bernard, 1955-1958 (Folder 352.53)
    - Berenson, Bernard, 1959 (Folder 182.16)
    - Bergauer, E.A. (Stella), 1952 Feb 28 (Folder 342.21)
    - Bergler, Edmund, 1942 June 4 (Folder 342.22)
    - Berlin, Isaiah, 1952, 1962-1977 (Folder 182.17)
    - Berman, Eugene, 1957-1961 (Folder 182.18)
    - Berman, Eugene, 1958 Sep 4 (Folder 342.23)
    - Berman, Sylvia and Leonid, 1961-1977 (Folder 182.19)
    - Berman, Leonid, 1953-1954, undated (Folder 342.24)
    - Bernier, Rosamond, 1964-1972, undated (Folder 182.20)
    - Berryman, John, 20 October 1949 (Folder 352.13)
    - Bewley, Marius, 1952, 1959 (Folder 342.26)
    - Biddle, Francis, 1952 Feb 28 (Folder 342.27)
    - Biehl, Walter (to the New Yorker), 1951 Dec 14 (Folder 342.28)
    - Biggs, John, Jr., 1963-1976 (Folder 183.1)
    - Biggs, John, Jr., 1952-1958 (Folder 342.29)
    - Bishop, Alison Lurie, 1967 (Folder 183.2)
    - Bishop, Elizabeth, 1978-1979, undated (Folder 183.3)
    - Bishop, Elizabeth, 1942, 1945, 1952 (Folder 342.30)
    - Bisset, Virgil, 1988-1989 (Folder 342.31)
    - Black, George Johnson, 1938 (Folder 343.1)
    - Blais, Marie-Claire, 1972-1977, undated (Folder 183.4)
    - Blake, Dorothy, 1981, undated (Folder 183.5)
    - Blanc, Karin, 1982-1986, undated (Folder 183.6)
    - Bledsoe, Helen W., 1980 Nov 5 (Folder 343.2)
    - Bloch, Vivette, 1988-1989 (Folder 343.3)
    - Blocker, Joel, 1968-1978 (Folder 183.7)
    - Blum, Jack, 1976-1983 (Folder 183.8)
    - Boel, Niels and Else, 1972-1988, undated (Folders 183.9 - 183.10)
    - Boel, Else and Bent, 1984, 1989, undated (Folder 343.5)
    - Boldizsár, Ivan, 1965-1980, undated (Folder 183.11)
    - Bondy, François, 1971-1985, undated (Folders 183.12 - 183.13)
    - Bondy, François, 1989 (Folder 343.6)
    - Bonser, Tony (Folder 343.7)
    - Bonwit, Seymour ["Bonnie"], 1983-1985 (Folder 183.14)
    - Booth, Margaret (Folder 352.14)
    - Booth, Philip (and Margaret), 1967-1975 (Folders 183.15 - 183.16)
    - Booth, Philip, 1976-1988, undated (Folders 184.1 - 184.6)
    - Booth, Philip, 1971, 1989, undated (Folder 343.7)
    - Botsford, Keith, 1965 (Folder 184.7)
    - Bondy, Francois (Folder 343.8)
    - Bouttelant, Jessie, 1970 (Folder 184.8)
    - [Boyden, Polly?] to Edmund Wilson (Folder 352.54)
    - Brady, Mary, 1968-1971, undated (Folders 184.9 - 184.10)
    - Braun-Monk, Eugène, 1979-1987, undated (Folder 185.1)
    - Brazier, Mary "Mollie" A. B., 1952 Feb 25 (Folder 343.9)
    - Breed, Rosilla Hornblower, 1949, 1954, 1956, undated (Folder 343.10)
    - Breit, Harvey, 1948, 1950 (Folder 352. 15)
    - Bresson, Charlotte and Edgar de, 1973-1989 (Folder 185.2)
    - Bresson, Edgar and Charlotte de, 1983 (Folder 352.16)
    - Breuer, Bessie, undated (Folder 185.3)
    - Brightman, Carol, 1989 (Folder 343.11)
    - Brinnin, John, 1980 (Folder 185.4)
    - Broch, Anne Marie ("Bushy"), 1976 -1987 (Folder 185.5)
    - Brocke, Edna, 1988 Oct 31 (Folder 343.12)
    - Brooks, Franklin, 1980-1981 (Folder 185.6)
    - Browar, Lisa, 1989 (Folder 343.13)
    - Brown, Andrew, 1979-1980 (Folder 343.14)
    - Brown, Ashley, 1987-1988 (Folder 343.15)
    - Brown, Mary Duer, 1981 (Folder 185.7)
    - Brown, Peg, 1965 (Folder 185.8)
    - Brownell, Sonia, 1948-1949 (Folder 343.16)
    - Bruzzichelli, Aldo, 1961-1981, undated (Folder 185.9)
    - Buckley, Gail, 1984-1985, undated (Folder 185.10)
    - Buckley, Tom, 1969-1985, undated (Folder 185.11)
    - Buitenhuis, Peter (Yale University), 1958 Apr 15 (Folder 343.17)
    - Burdick, Eugene, 1964 (Folder 185.12)
    - Burdick, Eugene, 1952-1956 (Folder 343.18)
    - Burdon-Mueller, Rowland, 1959-1980, undated (Folders 185.13 - 185.14)
    - Burgess, Anthony, 1977 (Folder 186.1)
    - Burroughs, William, 1971-1984 (Folder 186.2)
    - Bush, G. F., 1988 (Folder 343.19)
    - Cabot, Francis H., 1983-1986 (Folder 186.3)
    - Calvino, Italo and Chichita, 1977-1988, undated (Folder 186.4)
    - Calvino, Chichita, 1989 (Folder 343.20)
    - Cameron, Dorothy and Ray, 1977-1982, undated (Folder 186.5)
    - Campbell, Shelda, 1965, undated (Folder 186.6)
    - Camus, Albert (Folder 343.21)
    - Carr, Virginia Spencer, 1978-1986 (Folder 186.7)
    - Cartier-Bresson, Henri, 1974-1977 (Folder 186.8)
    - Chambers, Virginia, 1975-1978 (Folder 186.9)
    - Chapman, Bill, 1978 (Folder 186.10)
    - Chase, Richard, 1949-1950, undated (Folder 343.22)
    - Cheremeteff, Serge, 1950, 1956 (Folder 343.23)
    - Cherington, Charles, undated (Folder 343.24)
    - Chiaromonte, Anna, 1963-1964, no year (Folder 186.11)
    - Chiaromonte, Miriam, 1972-1988; [carbons of MM's letters to Chiaromonte (Folder 187.1)
    - Chiaromonte, Miriam, 1960-1988 (Folders 187.2 - 187.7)
    - Chiaromonte, Miriam, 1948-1955, 1989 (Folder 343.25)
    - Chiaromonte, Nicola, [Photocopies — original letters are at the Beinecke Library, Yale University] (Folder 187.8)
    - Chiaromonte, Nicola, 1946-1971, undated (Folders 187.9 - 187.14)
    - Chiaromonte, Nicola, 1948-1967 (Folder 344.1)
    - Childs, Bernard, 1965; (1 ms note and an engraving by Childs entitled "Stage Set" inscribed to McCarthy) (Folder 188.1)
    - Chirac, Jacques, 1989, July 8 (Folder 344.2)
    - Chisholm, Anne, 1974 (Folder 188.2)
    - Cicogna, Countess Anna Maria, 1957-1983, undated (Folder 188.3)
    - Cicogna, Anna Maria, 1957-1959, 1989 (Folder 344.3)
    - Clark, Blair, 1964-1967, undated (Folder 188.4)
    - Cody, Morrill, 1962-1978 (Folder 188.5)
    - Coffin, Frank M. and Ruth, 1969-1983 (Folder 188.6)
    - Coggeshall, Helen, 1949 Apr 14 (Folder 344.4)
    - Cohen, Elliot, 1949-1950 (Folder 344.5)
    - Cohen, Winnie, 1949, 1961 (Folder 188.7)
    - Colbath, Arnold and Mary Lou, 1982-1988 (Folder 188.8)
    - Cole, William, 1953 Sep 15 (Folder 344.6)
    - Collete, Margot, 1955 (Folder 344.7)
    - Colos, Nico, 1958 March 10 (Folder 344.8)
    - Compton-Burnett, Ivy, 1965 (Folder 188.9)
    - Comsa, Ioan, 1976-1977 (Folder 188.10)
    - Condé, Miquel and Carola, 1975-1988, undated (Folder 188.11)
    - Connolly, Cyril and Deirdre, 1947-1949, undated (Folder 344.9)
    - Coresagra, Sophia, 1989, undated (Folder 344.10)
    - Cori, Carl and Anne, 1969-1984 (Folders 188.12 - 188.14)
    - Cori, Anne, 1985-1988 (Folder 189.1)
    - Cori, Carl and Anne, undated (Folders 189.2 - 189.3)
    - Cori, Anne and Carl (Folder 352.17)
    - Corn, Alfred, 1989 (Folder 344.11)
    - Cox, Mary, 1952 (Folder 344.12)
    - Cozzens, James Gould, 1978 (Folder 189.4)
    - Curley, Tom, 1977, undated (Folder 189.5)
    - Curtin, John D., 1983-1985, undated (Folder 189.6)
    - Curtis, Charlotte, 1979 (Folder 189.7)
    - Curtiss, Thomas Quinn, 1980-1988, undated (Folder 189.8)
    - Curtiss, Thomas Quinn, 1988 Dec 19 (Folder 344.13)
    - Danesi, Natalia Murray, 1977 (Folder 189.9)
    - Daniels, Elizabeth, 1979 (Folder 189.10)
    - Dauphin, Ruda, 1970-1979, undated (Folder 189.11)
    - Davenport, John, 1956-1958 (Folder 189.12)
    - McCarthy-Davenport, 1956-1958 (Folder 189.13)
    - Davis, Hallie Flanagan (Smith College), 1942 Aug 27 (Folder 344.14)
    - Dean, Elizabeth, 1983 (Folder 344.15)
    - DeForest, Mary, 1989 (Folder 344.16)
    - De la Baumelle, Beatrice, 1978 (Folder 190.1)
    - Dellinger, Dave — Commitee To Defend the Conspiracy, (1 holiday card) (Folder 352.18)
    - de Man, Paul, 1949-1951, undated (Folder 344.17)
    - Deming, Barbara, 1954-1958 (Folder 352.19)
    - Deming, Barbara, 1959-1975, undated (Folders 190.2 - 190.4)
    - Deming, Vida (Mrs. Quentin), 1977-1984, undated (Folder 190.5)
    - DeMott, Maddie, 1971-1986 (Folder 190.6)
    - Den Uyl, Mrs., 1975 (Folder 190.7)
    - de Onis, Harriet, 1951 July 10 (Folder 344.18)
    - Derry, William R., 1976 (Folder 190.8)
    - Desmarais, Joan, 1961 (Folder 190.9)
    - Deutsch, Babette, 1976 (Folder 190.10)
    - Devoto, Bernard, 1952 Feb 13 (Folder 344.19)
    - Di Capua, Michael, 1962-1966 (Folder 394.19)
    - Dickerson, James, 1958 Oct 13, undated (Folder 344.20)
    - Doblhoff, Anne Marie, undated (Folder 344.21)
    - Dodd, Edward H. Jr., 1954 Feb 24 (Folder 344.22)
    - Donkers, Jan, 1980-1985, undated (Folder 190.11)
    - Donkers, Jan, 1989 (Folder 344.23)
    - Donovan, Tom, 1962-1963 (Folder 190.12)
    - Dos Passos, John and Katy, [1942?] March 16 (Folder 352.20)
    - Dow, Christopher and Clare, 1969-1988, undated (Folders 190.13 - 190.15)
    - Dow, Christopher and Clare, 1989 (Folder 344.24)
    - Downie, Betty, undated (Folder 190.16)
    - Draper, Theodore, 1968-1987 (Folder 190.17)
    - Droëmer, Willy, 1972 (Folder 190.18)
    - Duff, Robin, 1979-1980 (Folder 190.19)
    - Duffy, James, 1978 (Folder 190.20)
    - Dupee, Fred and Andy (Mrs.), 1962-1989, undated (Folder 191.1)
    - Dupee, Fred and Andy, 1939-1942, 1952, 1989, undated (Folder 344.25)
    - Dupee, Natalie and Tony, 1986-1988, undated (Folder 191.2)
    - DuVivier, David and Ellie, 1965-1979 (Folders 191.3 - 191.10)
    - DuVivier, David and Ellie, 1980-1985 (Folders 192.1 - 192.4)
    - DuVivier, David and Ellie, 1986-1987 (Folder 192.5)
    - DuVivier, David, undated (Folders 192.6 - 192.9)
    - DuVivier, David and Georgina, 1986-1989 (Folder 192.10)
    - [Duvivier, Ellie ?] (Folder 352.21)
    - Dyer, George, 1967 (Folder 193.1)
    - Eagleson, Jeannie, 1978 (Folder 193.2)
    - Eaton, Richard, 1982, 1989 (Folder 344.26)
    - Eberhart, Richard, 1984 (Folder 193.3)
    - Eckstein, Joanna, 1965-1970 (Folder 193.4)
    - Edey, Winthrop, 1959 May 5 (Folder 344.27)
    - Englund, Steven, 1974 (Folder 193.5)
    - Ephessiou, Lisa, 1978 (Folder 193.6)
    - Epstein, Barbara, 1972, undated (Folder 193.7)
    - Epstein, Barbara, 1981, 1988 (Folder 352.22)
    - Epstein, Jacob, 1981 (Folder 193.8)
    - Epstein, Jason, 1975 (Folder 193.9)
    - Errera, Roger, 1977-1984, undated (Folder 193.10)
    - Evans, Bergen, 1959 (Folder 193.11)
    - Evans, Walter (Fortune), 1956 May 24 (Folder 344.28)
    - Eynard, Jean-Francois, 1989 (Folder 344.29)
    - Fairholme, Anne, 1965-1980 (Folder 193.12)
    - Fairweather, Gloria, 1972-1973 (Folder 193.13)
    - Fallaci, Oriana, 1967 (Folder 193.14)
    - Farrell, James, 1967-1979, undated (Folders 193.15 - 193.16)
    - Farrell, James, 1952 March 30 (Folder 344.30)
    - Faulkner, William, 1956 Oct 11 (Folder 344.31)
    - Feitelson, Rose, 1954, 1986 (Folder 344.32)
    - Finletter, Tom and Eileen, 1968-1982, undated (Folders 193.17 - 193.19)
    - Fitts, Dudley, circa 1951-1952 (Folder 344.33)
    - FitzGerald, Frances "Frankie", 1964-1987, undated (Folder 194.1)
    - Fitzgerald, Frances "Frankie,", 25 August 1989 (Folder 352.23)
    - Fitzgerald, undated (Folder 344.34)
    - Flagler, Elizabeth, 1989 Apr 20 (Folder 344.35)
    - Flanner, Janet, 1959-1970, undated (Folder 194.2)
    - Fleutiaux, Pierrette, 1977 (Folder 194.3)
    - Flynn, Thomas, 1952-1953 (Folder 344.36)
    - Fondaras, Liz, 1974-1985 (Folder 194.4)
    - Ford, Charles Henri, 1960-1985, undated (Folders 194.5 - 194.6)
    - Ford, Charles Henri and Indra Bahadur Tamang, 1952-1957, 1983, undated (Folder 345.1)
    - Ford, Ruth, 1964, undated (Folder 194.7)
    - Foster, E. A., 1954 (Folder 345.2)
    - Foster, Eleanor, 1968-1973 (Folder 194.8)
    - Fourrier, Maria, 1973-1985, undated (Folders 194.9 - 194.10)
    - Fowler, Pat, 1982-1989, undated (Folder 168.2)
    - Fowler, Pat, 1989 (Folder 339.4)
    - Frank, Joseph, 1962-1981, undated (Folder 194.11)
    - Frank, Joseph, 1984 (Folder 352.24)
    - Frank, Richard L., 1941-1942 (Folder 345.3)
    - Frank, Waldo, 1954 (Folder 345.4)
    - Fredericks, Claude, 1960, undated (Folder 195.1)
    - Freire, Carlos and Heloisa, 1977-1988 (Folder 195.2- 195.9)
    - Freiere, Carlos, 1989 (Folder 345.5)
    - Freire, Heloisa, 1989 (Folder 345.6)
    - Fremantle, A., 1967 (Folder 196.1)
    - Frere, A. S., 1962-1963 (Folder 196.2)
    - Frere, A. S., 1954-1958 (Folder 345.10)
    - Fuller, Buckminster, 1971 (Folder 352.25)
    - Fuller, Mia, 1989 (Folder 345.7)
    - Fuller, Muriel, 1954 (Folder 345.8)
    - Fuller, Peta, 1953 (Folder 345.9)
    - Gaddis, William and Sarah, 1984-1988, undated (Folder 196.3)
    - Gahan, Martha, undated (Folder 345.11)
    - Gaines, Joan Becker, 1964 (Folder 196.4)
    - Gaitskell, Hugh, 1955 (Folder 349.22)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1968-1969 (Folder 196.5)
    - Ganguli, P. B. and A. K., 1968-1979 (Folder 196.6)
    - Garzanti, Livio (Aldo Garzanti Editore), 1958 (Folder 345.12)
    - Gascoigne, Bamber, undated (Folder 196.7)
    - Gassler, Eve, 1947-1949 (Folder 345.13)
    - Gaus, John (Harvard University), 1952 (Folder 345.14)
    - Geist, Eileen, 1956 (Folder 345.16)
    - Geist, Stanley, 1949-1951 (Folder 345.17)
    - Geist, Stanley, 1971-1984, undated (Folder 196.8)
    - Gelderman, Carol (Biographer), 1981, 1989 (Folder 345.18)
    - Gentier, A., undated (Folder 196.9)
    - George, Lillian, undated (Folder 196.10)
    - George, Lillian, undated (Folder 345.19)
    - George, Susan, 1973 Sep 25 (Folder 343.20)
    - Geppini, Sabatina [Housekeeper], 1959-1969 (Folder 196.11)
    - Gerbore, Pietro, 1959-1963 (Folder 196.12)
    - Gerbore, Pietro, 1957-1958 (Folder 345.19)
    - Gilbert, Elke Elizabeth, 1974-1976, undated (Folder 196.13)
    - Gill, Brendan re: Jay Rousuck, 1971-1980 (Folder 196.14)
    - Gill, Brandan, 1952 (Folder 345.22)
    - Gilliat, Penelope, 1975-1976 (Folder 196.15)
    - Girodias, Maurice, 1978-1985 (Folder 196.16)
    - Giroux, Robert, 1949 (Folder 345.23)
    - Gladstone, Peter, undated (Folder 345.24)
    - Glanville, Brian, 1958 (Folder 345.25)
    - Glick, Nathan (Department of State), 1951-1952 (Folder 345.26)
    - Goetz, Fione, undated (Folder 196.17)
    - Goldwater, Walter, 1979-1984, no year (Folder 196.18)
    - Goodheart, Pat and Gene, 1966-1980, undated (Folder 197.1)
    - Goodwin, Jackie and Francis, 1980-1988 (Folder 197.2)
    - Goodwin, Jacquie, 1989 (Folder 345.27)
    - Gordey, Beverly and Michel, 1969-1978 (Folder 197.3)
    - Gorer, Geoffrey, 1967 (Folder 197.4)
    - Gottstein, Burton (Folder 345.28)
    - Grand-Jacquet, Francesco, 1982, undated (Folder 197.5)
    - Gray, Elizabeth Kent (Folder 345.29)
    - Gray, Francine, 1984-1988 (Folder 197.6)
    - Grchich de Cvetkovacz, Alexandre (Polly), undated (Folder 197.7)
    - Grebanier, Bernard — regarding The Stones of Venice, 20 December 1956 (Folder 352.26)
    - Green, Martha, 1964 (Folder 197.8)
    - Greenberg, Clement (Folder 345.30)
    - Greer, Germaine, 1971-1972 (Folder 197.9)
    - Grenier, Cynthia and Richard, 1964-1978, undated (Folder 197.10)
    - Griffith, Christina, 1988 (Folder 197.11)
    - Groffsky, Maxine, 1965, undated (Folder 197.12)
    - Gross, Miriam and John, 1965 (Folder 197.13)
    - Grübel, Jona, 1978, undated (Folder 197.14)
    - Guggenheim, Peggy, circa, 1950-1980 (Folder 197.15)
    - Guggeinheim, Peggy (Folder 345.31)
    - Gurian, Waldemar (Folder 345.32)
    - Gustafson, Carolyn, 1964, undated (Folder 197.16)
    - Gysin, Brion, 1969-1979 (Folder 197.17)
    - Hackett, "Bubs", 1981-1987, undated (Folder 197.18)
    - Hadlock, Josephine Cook [VC 1933], 1982, no year (Folder 197.19)
    - Haight, Gordon S., 1979-1984 (Folder 197.20)
    - Haight, Gordon (Yale University) (Folder 345.33)
    - Hall, Suzanne and David, 1984-1988 (Folder 197.21)
    - Hall, Suzannah, 1989 (Folder 345.34)
    - Hamilton, Hamish "Jamie", 1958-1959, undated (Folder 345.35)
    - Harari, Denyse, 1973-1987 (Folder 197.22)
    - Haraszti, Miklos (Folder 345.36)
    - Hardwick, Elizabeth, 1953-1988, undated (Folders 198.1 - 198.9)
    - Hardwick, Elizabeth (Folder 345.37)
    - Hargreaves, John, 1977-1988, undated (Folder 199.1)
    - Hargreaves, John (Folder 345.38)
    - Harkell, Francis (Folder 345.39)
    - Harnden, Missy, 1972-1976 (Folder 199.2)
    - Harris, Anne and Russell, 196-?,1982, undated (Folder 199.3)
    - Hartmann, Chris, 1980-1984, undated (Folder 199.4)